[
    {
        "category":"Bootstrap",
        "type":"multiple",
        "difficulty":"easy",
        "question":"Which of the following bootstrap styles are used to add a dropdown to a tab?",
        "correct_answer":"\nnav, .nav-tabs, dropdown-.menu",
        "incorrect_answers":[
        "nav, .nav-tabs, .menu","nav, .nav-pills, .dropdown","nav, .nav-pills"
        ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Bootstrap",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Which of the following class applies the hover color to a particular row or cell of a table?",
      "correct_answer": "active",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "success",
        "warning",
        "danger"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Bootstrap",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "question": "Which of the following bootstrap style of button indicates caution should be taken with this action?",
      "correct_answer": "btn-warning",
      "incorrect_answers": ["btn-danger", "btn-link", "btn-info"]
    },
    {
      "category": "Bootstrap",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Which of the following bootstrap styles are used to create a vertical pills navigation?",
      "correct_answer": ".nav, .nav-pills, .nav-stacked",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        ".nav, .nav-tabs",
        ".nav, .nav-pills",
        ".nav, .nav-tabs, .nav-justified"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Bootstrap",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which class indicates a dropdown menu?",
      "correct_answer": ".dropdown",
      "incorrect_answers": [".dropdown-list", ".select", "null"]
    },
    {
      "category": "Bootstrap",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "A standard navigation tab is created with:",
      "correct_answer": "<ul class=”nav tabs”>",
      "incorrect_answers": ["<ul class=”navigation-tabs”>", "<ul class=”navnav-tabs”>", "<ul class=”navnav-navbar”>"]
    },
    {
      "category": "Bootstrap",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": " Which class is used to create a black navigation bar?",
      "correct_answer": ".navbar-inverse",
      "incorrect_answers": [".navbar-dark", ".navbar-black", ".navbar-default"]
    },
    {
      "category": "Bootstrap",
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Which plugin is used to create a tooltip?",
      "correct_answer": "tooltip",
      "incorrect_answers": [" modal"," dialog Box"," popup"]
    },
    {
      "category": "Bootstrap",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Default size of H5 bootstrap heading",
      "correct_answer": "14px",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "16px",
        "18px",
        "20px"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Bootstrap",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which class creates pagination?",
      "correct_answer": "pagination",
      "incorrect_answers": ["pager","pagination-link"," link-pagination"]
    }
  ]
  